Prudential has been
fully committed to long-term protection planning for savings policy customers for more than 170 years
Prudential proactively discloses policy returns to stand the test of time
S&P global rating upgraded to AA Working
with the world's top investment partners, using its local advantages!
Local advantage?  What does it mean?
Just like drinking milk tea, you need
to find a gold medal master to make it!
He needs to be familiar with the tastes of the neighbors
in order to brew a fragrant, rich and smooth authentic gold medal milk tea
so when you find the right master, half the battle!
In the same way, our investment partners must be familiar with the local market to
fight for long-term and robust returns for our participating policy clients
Understand!  Please have a cup of golden milk tea!